<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SARSys on DISCO Open Source</title><link>https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/</link><description>Recent content in SARSys on DISCO Open Source</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:31:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SARSys</title><link>https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/tos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:31:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/tos/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Terms of Use&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that
you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app,
or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also
shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the
trademarks, copyright, database rights, and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to
DISCO Open Source.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sarsys</title><link>https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/privacy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.discoos.org/projects/sarsys/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Privacy Policy&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>DISCO Open Source built the SARSys app as an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by DISCO Open Source at no
cost and is intended for use as is.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal
Information if anyone decided to use our Service.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this
policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use
or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>